blowoutcards.com 2009-06-19

# Privacy Policy : Blowout Cards - Sports Cards and Trading Cards Wholesale Online Store

**How is my personal information protected?**

Blowout Cards uses industry standard security techniques on our web site to help protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected from you from the Blowout Cards web site. When you access your account information or transmit personally identifiable data to the Blowout Cards web site, that information is stored on servers that the we have attempted to secure from unauthorized access or intrusion. "Secure Socket Layer" software encrypts all personal information you transmit to the Blowout Cards web site. Blowout Cards cannot be and is not responsible for unauthorized access to information by hackers or others who have obtained such access through illegal measures.

When shopping with us online, we have security measures in place and take reasonable precautions to protect against the loss, misuse and unauthorized access of your personal information under our control. Blowout Cards cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us by e-mail, and you do so at your own risk.

 **Safe Shopping Policy on BlowoutCards.com**

Because the security of your personal information is a high priority, we have taken numerous steps to ensure that it is processed confidentially, accurately and securely. The Blowout Cards web site uses encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL encrypts ordering information such as your name, address and credit card number. 

**What are cookies and how does Blowout Cards use them?**

Blowoutcards.com uses "cookies," which are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. The cookies are used to create a more personalized shopping experience for visitors to our site.  Cookies simulate a continuous connection — they let us "remember" information about your preferences and session, and allow you to move within areas of our Web sites without reintroducing yourself.  (Some examples of this data include your account preferences or items previously saved to your shopping cart.) We do not use cookies to store any of your personal or financial information on your computer. 

You may choose to set your Web browser to not accept cookies. If your cookies are disabled, you can still view our site, but you cannot create an account, login to your account or make purchases.

 **Blowout Cards does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties.**

We may need to share your personal information with certain third parties such as our agents, service providers and other representatives acting on our behalf for limited purposes. For example, we may share personal information with third parties to perform services on our behalf such as:

  * Fulfilling our customers' orders
  * Sending Blowout Cards marketing communications
  * Delivering packages
  * Sending regular mail and e-mail on behalf of Blowout Cards
  * Processing credit card payments 

The third parties with whom we conduct business are only authorized to use your information to perform the service for which they were hired. As part of our agreement with them, they are required to follow the privacy guidelines we provide them and to take reasonable measures to ensure your personal information is secure.
